Sandy Lin

160 Trimbleston Goatstown road clonskeagh Dublin 14 D14DD43 | 353 89 989 5309 | https://sandylin520.github.io/RS/ | https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-l-b97150117/ | b810521@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I have 6+ years of experience in sales, client management, account development and cooperation with cross functional global teams. My past experience focuses on B-to-B Service, I helped the enterprise build brand loyalty by promptly responding to client needs. Other than that, I also provided a high-level technical support to reduce engineering workload, troubleshoot system problems to ensure the accuracy of the cash flow and mail delivery.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration

Yuan Ze university | September 2010 – June 2014

Exchange Student Program

City University of Hong Kong | August 2013 – December 2013

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Underwriters Laboratories | Client Service Specialist Taipei, Taiwan | September 2015 - May 2021

- Achieve referral business opportunity target \$15K across division
- Meet 90% of assigned myUL email campaign customer registered
- Manage 53 product categories in domestic wire and cable industry.
- Provide training to colleagues on programs and processes, technical support to in house employees
- Encourage 150+ clients to register for new platform, MyUL Portal in 2019
- Meet internal KPI target (92% of Engineer Support team e-Mail responses within 24hrs & 94% of personal e-Mail responses within 24hrs in 2015~2021)
- Support global team to implement system successfully
- Support Sales to help key account customer register MyUL successfully
- Collaborate and coordinate with Operations, Support Services, Quality Assurance, Sales, Business Development and other affiliated stakeholders to ensure that clients experience superior service.
- Assist customers with project management and assist local collection team to ensure accuracy of invoices to meet cash flow targets
- Build up new service knowledge to align with division business strategies
- Participate in trade shows and technical conferences, present obtained knowledge and information to team or coworkers after event
- Determine customer needs and guide them to make decisions about product certification
- Classify customers, update and maintain customer database (Internal oracle database, MyUL Product IQ, My UL Portal)
- Provide quotes, organize and process samples for assigned client accounts

Ezfly International Travel Agent Co Ltd | Wholesaler Taipei, Taiwan | March 2015 - September 2015

- Sell group tours and tour packages to retail travel agents
- Participate in travel exhibitions and sell tours to customers
- Highest monthly sales revenue record: NT\$ 1 million

Sandy Lin

160 Trimbleston Goatstown road clonskeagh Dublin 14 D14DD43 | 353 89 989 5309 | https://sandylin520.github.io/RS/ | https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-l-b97150117/ | b810521@gmail.com

LANGUAGE

Chinese: Native English: Fluent German: Basic

SKILLS

Customer Satisfaction

Teamwork

Communication:

Oracle

Web Application Development, Python, SQL

INTERESTS

In my spare time, I like to learn new technology and try finding out how technology makes my life easier and better.(https://sandylin520.github.io/RS/)